tidefans.com 2001-06-02

# BBS Policy

****

**Privacy Statement for TideFans.com**

**TideFans.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [TideFans.com](http://tidefans.com/)

**Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. IP addresses are also logged within the message boards.  These do not identify any specific person, but help us in maintaining site and board security.  This information is not disseminated in any way other than at a macro level (i.e. we received 100000 page views from 1000 different IP addresses) to any outside source.

**Cookies**

Our Site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your preferences on the message boards. We also use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.  Other cookies may be set by advertising banners.  See the Third Party Relationships section below.

**Advertisers**

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad server, and we do not have access to this information.

**Registration Forms**

Our site message board registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), unique identifiers (username and password), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).

Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary and to administrate the message board and other features of the site (like TideFans.com branded email and TideFans.com branded personal websites).

Users may opt-out of receiving mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Unique identifiers (such as email addresses) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity, and for use as account numbers in our record system.

**Surveys**

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like email address).  We gather various demographic information that we may make available to advertisers at a macro level (i.e. we have 5000 users who live in Alabama and are ages 35-45).

Users may opt-out of receiving any mailings from the site; see the choice/opt-out section below.

**Contests**

We occasionally run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like email address), and unique identifiers (like username).

Contact information from the contests is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary to inform them of results of the contests..

Unique identifiers are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity, and for use as account numbers in our record system. 

We do not provide this information to a third party unless noted in the contest. 

**External Links**

This site contains _thousands_ of links to other sites. **TideFans.com** is not in any way responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites and only supplies these links as a "public service" to our users.  If you should find a link that you believe we should remove, please contact us immediately at [admin@tidefans.com](mailto:admin@tidefans.com).

**Special Third Party Relationships**

**TideFans.com** provides several services that, while being TideFans.com branded, are administered by third parties.

Our @TideFans.com email service is administered by [Everyone.net](http://everyone.net/)

Our [ YourSite.TideFans.com](http://signup.tidefans.com/) free webspace service is administered by [CommunityArchitect.com](http://communityarchitect.com/).

Our  Alabama Weekly newsletter list is maintained at [ListBot.com](http://listbot.com/).

Our Advertising banners are provided through the [About.com](http://about.com/) [Luna Network](http://lunanetwork.com/) via the [DoubleClick.net](http://doubleclick.net/) service.

You can visit each of these sites to ascertain the level of privacy by each of these sites.  We have selected these partners because they are the "best of breed" services and provide great, reliable, and free services to our users.

**Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, newsletters available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas immediately becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

This site provides various services of which we are able to distribute occasional information via email.  However, in each of these, you can opt out of receiving any future emails.

Alabama Weekly Newsletter:  [bamanation-unsubscribe@listbot.com](mailto:bamanation-unsubscribe@listbot.com) 

Email and Message Board registrations can be setup so that the user doesn't receive any emails from the TideFans.com staff.  However, as these are used only to disseminate critical information pertaining to the site, we do not recommend you eliminate your email from our distribution list.  We do not make this list available to any third party.

**Data Quality/Access**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:

Message Boards & Email:  You can modify personal information provided about yourself in the message board by clicking "Preferences" or "Profile" in the message boards or "Options" in email. 

Other:  You can send email to:  [admin@TideFans.com](mailto:admin@TideFans.com) to request a change.  Some "changes" actually require inactivating an account and setting up a new one.  Email us for more details

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact any of the following:

Brett Young  
Managing Editor & Site Administrator  
TideFans.com & Alabama Weekly  
Partner, BamaNation Partners, LLC[  
admin@TideFans.com](mailto:admin@TideFans.com)

Hunter Ray   
Partner, BamaNation Partners, LLC  

Jim Morris  
Features Editor[  
](mailto:Editor%0d%0aJim.Morris@TideFans.com) TideFans.com & Alabama Weekly[  
Jim.Morris@TideFans.com](mailto:Editor%0d%0aJim.Morris@TideFans.com)

Jess Nicholas  
Editor at Large  
TideFans.com & Alabama [ Weekly  
JessN@TideFans.com](mailto:Weekly%0d%0aJessN@TideFans.com)
